#### Contact

maeda.solomon@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ maedasolomon (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Healthcare

Nursing

Informatics

#### Certifications

Project Management Professional (PMP)

# Maeda Solomon

Sr. Project Manager, Provider Data Performance Manager; at UnitedHealthcare

Greater Nashville Area, TN

## Summary

Healthcare and information technology professional with a diverse skill set comprised of patient care, academic research, clinical informatics, process improvement, agile and waterfall SDLC, project management, HEDIS® based quality and provider data performance management, accountable care, contracting and payer data exchange experience. Proven success at leading, managing, and negotiating multiple concurrent large-scale projects.

## Experience

UnitedHealth Group

4 years 7 months

Sr. Project Manager, Provider Data Performance Manager January 2019 - Present (1 year 6 months)

Greater Nashville Area, TN

Sr. Clinical Practice Consultant
December 2015 - January 2019 (3 years 2 months)

LifePoint Hospitals
Director of Clinical Informatics
July 2013 - February 2015 (1 year 8 months)

MEDHOST EHR Product Manager April 2011 - June 2013 (2 years 3 months)

#### **HCA**

Health Information Technology Manager July 2010 - April 2011 (10 months)

Delta Medical Center of Memphis Clinical Informatics Coordinator April 2009 - July 2010 (1 year 4 months)

Methodist Healthcare
PACU Nurse
August 2003 - July 2010 (7 years)

University of Tennessee Health Science Center Research Nurse Coordinator November 2003 - April 2009 (5 years 6 months)

OR Nurses, Inc.
Agency Registered Nurse
October 2003 - November 2006 (3 years 2 months)
Greater Memphis Area

Cross Country Healthcare
Travel Registered Nurse
October 2002 - October 2003 (1 year 1 month)
Oakland, California - Kaiser Permanente

Baptist Memorial Health Care Critical Care Registered Nurse September 1999 - January 2003 (3 years 5 months)

US Army
Radio Repairer - 29E, Communication Technology
May 1990 - May 1994 (4 years 1 month)
Fort Campbell, KY and Camp Humphreys, South Korea

## Education

The University of Tennessee Health Science Center Master of Science, Healthcare Informatics and Information Management · (2007 - 2009)

Clayton State University
Bachelor of Science, Nursing (1996 - 1998)